This is Ritesh's branch


After login of admin, not only the token should come, but also the other details should come like name....

and also the same thing for the other users...

register user ma null check garya xaina, tyo null check garnu parxa ya undefined check garnu parxa, validation ni use garnu parxa.....

Register user ma also use the Try Catch (Express Validation use garnu parxa)

null password halda, field fill gar msg aaunu paro instead of invalid email or password

stack ma aaune error lai milaune, kina error aai rya xa, proper details ma milaune 

Add change password features
